Do you give?
Pillion is a romance, drama, comedy film directed by Harry Lighton.
Colin, a timid man is swept off his feet when Ray, an enigmatic,
impossibly handsome biker takes him on as his submissive.
Colin, played by Harry Melling.
Ray, played by Alexander Skarsgård.
Peggy, played by Lesley Sharp.
Pete, played by Douglas Hodge.
Kevin, played by Jake Shears.
Steve, played by Mat Hill.
Pillion is a 2025 romantic black comedy drama film written and directed by Harry
Lighton, based on the 2020 novel Box Hill by Adam Mars-Jones.
The film stars Harry Melling as a timid gay man and Alexander Skarsgård
as an enigmatic biker who start a BDSM relationship.
Pillion had its premiere in the Un Certain Regard section of the 2025 Cannes Film Festival on 18 May 2025, where it won the section's
Best Screenplay prize and the Palm Dog for Mutt Moment, alongside nominations for the Caméra d'Or and the Queer Palm.
It was released in the United Kingdom by Warner Bros.
Pictures and Picturehouse Entertainment on 28 November 2025.
The film received critical acclaim, receiving several nominations and awards, including
two British Independent Film Awards and a Gotham Independent Film Awards.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, dark
comedy, biker, male homosexuality, devotion.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.